http://www.medibadge.com/customer-service-W11C322.aspx#privacy

0
item(s):
$0
Catalog Quick Order|My Account|
Login
Shop Our Entire SelectionMedical & HospitalDentalBankingDanceSchool & DaycareHoliday & Seasonal
Dance
Call toll FREE:
800-228-0040
Or fax 24 hours:
Customer Service
FAQs    Satisfaction Guarantee    Returns Policy     Shipping & Payment Options   Promotional Offers International Orders     Privacy Policy     Comment/Question Form    Purchasing & Resale Policy
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
No Minimum Order
We are pleased to fill and ship your orders, regardless of the size. We require no minimum purchase.
5 Ways to Contact Us
Our friendly Customer Service Team is ready to take your order, answer your questions, or assist you in any way. With 5 easy ways to contact us, ordering has never been easier.
Order Online - Simply browse our online catalog, place selected items in your shopping cart and process the order when you're done. If you are shopping with a catalog and know your item numbers, use our handy Quick Order Form to quickly add several items to your shopping cart.
Call Toll Free 1-800-228-0040 for fast service throughout the U.S.A. and Canada. (Monday - Friday, 8am to 6pm, Eastern Standard Time.)
Fax Toll Free 1-800-546-1072, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. (International customers, please fax to: 402-571-1072.) Your order will receive prompt attention by our Customer Service Department. Printable Fax Form
E-Mail Address: stickers@MediBadge.com
Mail To: MediBadge, P.O. Box 12307, Omaha, NE, 68112
100% Satisfaction Guarantee
We are confident in our products and want you to be, too. That's why all of your MediBadge purchases are satisfaction guaranteed! If you are not 100% satisfied with your merchandise, you may exchange it or return it for a 100% refund. Just call us....it's that simple! If you are satisfied, please tell your friends. Large order returns may incur a restocking fee and will vary by order.
Easy Returns
If you are not fully satisfied with your merchandise, you may return it for a full refund. Custom printed products and special orders must be defective for return and have prior authorization from Customer Service. Shipping and handling are non-refundable.
Please call toll free 1-800-228-0040 to make arrangements with one of our friendly Customer Service Representatives. Please ship returns UPS, FedEx, or other insured mail to:
MediBadge, Inc. 7250 Reynolds Street Omaha, NE 68122
Fast Delivery - Shipping Rates
Order M-F by 3:00 p.m. EST and we'll ship your order today! Orders placed after 3:00 p.m. Friday will ship the following Monday. Internet orders placed on Saturday/Sunday are shipped the following Monday. We will contact you with any delays. Please allow 3-5 business days for standard Ground delivery. Shipping Fees are based on product purchase total:
Shipping Rates - Contiguous U.S.A.: Up to $59.99: $9.95 $60.00 - $119.99: $12.95 $120.00 - $249.99: $15.95 $250.00 - $499.99: $19.95 $500.00 and up: 5% of Order
Orders to AK and HI will ship via USPS or FedEx Ground. The shipping rates above apply, plus an additional $15.00 will be added to your order.
Canada:The shipping rates above apply, plus an additional $23.00 (USD) will be added to your order. (Brokerage/Entry fees for Canada shipments are included in this charge, and will not be owed upon delivery.)
GU, VI, and PR: The shipping rates above apply, plus an additional 15% of your Order Subtotal.
In a hurry? Next Day and Second Day FedEx are available upon your request. Additional charges determined by weight and zone will be added to your invoice. Please place your rush order by phone. Our Customer Service Team will gladly help you!
Specialty orders and custom orders may incur additional shipping charges depending on the weight and destination.
Handling charges may apply to orders billed to your FedEx account and will vary depending on the size of your order.
In certain circumstances we may require a signature for delivery. Orders requiring a signature will incur an additional charge.
Payment Options
If your order is being billed to a health care practice, professional corporation or is submitted on a purchase order form we will be happy to bill you. Completion of a credit application may be required. All sales are FOB Omaha, Nebraska and NET 10 days. For individuals, please pre-pay by check, money order, Master Card, Visa, American Express, or Discover Card. You may send your check or money order with your order:
MediBadge, Inc. P.O. Box 12307 Omaha, NE 68112
Please note: All prices on our website and in our catalog are in USD, and do not include sales tax, or any brokerage, duty, custom or GST fees.
Sales Tax:MediBadge, Inc. currently collects applicable sales tax for the following states:
AR, CA, CO, GA, IA, IL, IN, KY, LA, MD, ME, MI, MN, NC, NE, NJ, NV, OK, PA, SD, UT, VA, WA, WI, WV
Promotional Offers
MediBadge, Inc. reserves the right to accept or reject any orders, and also reserves the right to limit discounts, offers and purchase quantities. Promotional offers are subject to change or end with or without notice at any time. Distributors and Reseller are not eligible for promotional offers.
Purchasing and Resale Policy
MediBadge, Inc. products are not intended for resale.
MediBadge products may be purchased by Healthcare offices and professional businesses, and solely for the purpose of using as giveaway items and are not intended for resale. Licensed products may not be purchased by resellers. A reseller is defined as any individual or entity that purchases items from MediBadge, Inc. with the intent to sell. Permission is not granted to purchase licensed items to resell on online auction sites or other online retailers or storefronts.
MediBadge licensed stickers are intended for non-commercial use and may not be a) used to decorate other items which will thereafter be sold or b) bundled with other items which will thereafter be sold.
Promotional offers and discounts will not be honored on orders from resellers.
MediBadge, Inc. reserves the right to accept or reject any orders, and also reserves the right to limit discounts, offers and purchase quantities. Promotional offers are subject to change or end with or without notice at any time.
International Orders
Orders shipped outside the U.S.A. must be prepaid in U.S. funds by wire transfer. Orders shipped outside the U.S.A. will be sent via U.S. Mail. We will contact you with estimated shipping charges before processing your order. We reserve the right to refuse orders from countries to which we are unable to ship. All prices on our website and in our catalog are in U.S. funds and do not include any brokerage, duty, custom or GST fees.
Privacy Policy
Policy Regarding Information Privacy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  •To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) •To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) •To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) •To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
•To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
•To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.)
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'My Account' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. MediBadge markets children’s products to adults. We do not directly sell products to children. If you are under 18, you need the consent of a parent or guardian before making a purchase.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.kidslovestickers.com
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
www.kidslovestickers.com P.O. Box 12307 Omaha, NE 68112 United States stickers@medibadge.com 402-571-1800
This policy is powered by Trust Guard PCI compliance.
Policy Regarding Postal Mailings
If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services. Again, MediBadge does not share customer information with other companies or organizations for any purposes. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at 800-228-0040 or writing to us at the above address and telling us that you do not want to receive mailings from our company. You may also e-mail your request to stickers@MediBadge.com and type REMOVE FROM CATALOG MAILINGS in the subject line. Please provide us with your exact name and address in the body section of your message. We will make every attempt to insure that your name is removed from our mailing list.
The postal address for Customer Service at MediBadge is: MediBadge, Inc. P.O. Box 12307 Omaha, NE 68112
Policy Regarding Telephone Privacy
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online or as a follow up to comments and questions. Please provide us with your correct phone number. MediBadge does not share this customer information with other companies or organizations.
The telephone number for Customer Service at MediBadge is:800- 228-0040.
Copyright Information
The MediBadge website and all information contained in the site are the property of MediBadge, and are protected by law. All images displayed at this site are the property of MediBadge or their respective owners. Reproduction in whole or part is strictly prohibited.
Company Information
About MediBadge
Contact Us
Catalog Quick Order
Fax Form
Request a Catalog
Questions and Comments
Get Email Offers
VIP Savings Program
© 2019 MediBadge, Inc. reserves the right to accept or reject any orders, and also reserves the right to limit discounts, offers and purchase quantities. Character Licensed products may not be shipped outside the USA or Canada. All images displayed on this site are the property of MediBadge or their respective owners and may not be reproduced in any manner.
All information and prices are believed to be accurate but may be changed without notice.
MediBadge reserves the right to accept or reject any orders.
© Copyright 2019 MediBadge, Inc. All rights reserved.
Our Privacy Policy
